let API = [
  {
    Question: "Who is The Founder of Pakistan",
    Options: [
      "Muhammad Ali Jinnah",
      "Allama Iqbal",
      "Imran Khan",
      "Bibi Fatima",
    ],
    Answer: 0,
  },
  {
    Question: "Who is The Prime Minister of Pakistan",
    Options: [
      "Muhammad Ali Jinnah",
      "Allama Iqbal",
      "Imran Khan",
      "Bibi Fatima",
    ],
    Answer: 2,
  },
  {
    Question: "When Pakistan Founded",
    Options: ["14-Aug-1947", "14-Aug-1949", "14-Aug-1948", "14-Aug-1950"],
    Answer: 0,
  },
  {
    Question: "Expansion of CSK",
    Options: [
      "Chennai super kings",
      "royal challenges banglore",
      "punjab kings",
      "mumbai indians",
    ],
    Answer: 0,
  },{
    Question: "LVM3 is the largest rocket of which country?",
    Options: [
      "India",
      "Bangladesh",
      "Israel ",
      "Ukraine",
    ],
    Answer: 0,
  },
  {
      Question: "Cabinet approves LIGO-India gravitational-wave detector to be built in which state?",
      Options: [
        "Tamil Nadu",
        "Maharashtra",
        "Kerala ",
        "Odisha",
      ],
      Answer: 1,
  },
  {
    Question: "Which among the following was Indiaâ€™s first Teraflop supercomputer?",
    Options: [
      "PARAM 10000 ",
      "PARAM Yuva",
      "PARAM Padma ",
      "PARAM 9000/ss",
    ],
    Answer: 2,
},
{
  Question: "In what form is the data expressed in a digital computer?  ",
  Options: [
    "Binary ",
    "Tertiary",
    "Primary ",
    "SecondaryPARAM 10000",
  ],
  Answer: 0,
},

{
  Question: "What are four basic functional elements of a digital computer? ",
  Options: [
    "Input-Output Equipment",
    "Main Memory",
    "Control Unit and ALU ",
    "All of the above",
  ],
  Answer: 3,
},

{
  Question: " Who among the following gave the first theory related to computer software?",
  Options: [
    "Ada Lovelace",
    "Alan Turing",
    "Steve Jobs ",
    "Bill Gates",
  ],
  Answer: 1,
},

];

export default API;
